Guide to the Clive L. DuVal papers, 1960-1994
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 2: Legislative Files, 1966-1992
  - Subseries 2.2 - Legislative Studies, 1968-1992; (5 Boxes)
    - VEPCO Rate Case (pt 3), 1987-1988 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Northern Virginia Community College (pt 1), undated (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Northern Virginia Community College (pt 2), undated (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Northern Virginia Community College (pt 3), undated (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Northern Virginia Community College (pt 4), undated (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Out of State Students at Virginia Colleges, undated (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - P and E Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Private Prisons in Virginia, undated (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Recycling, undated (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Recycling Bill, 1988-1990 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Rules Committee, undated (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - School for Contemporary Education, undated (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Retirement Benefits, undated (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Retirement Benefits, undated (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Senior Citizens, undated (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - SLC Environmental Quality and Natural Resources, 1990-1991 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Solid Waste, undated (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Sound Barrier - Beltway - Balls Hill, undated (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Sound Barriers, Dunn Loring, etc., undated (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Southern Legislative Conference, undated (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Springfield Bypass, undated (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Standing of Citizens to Participate in State Administrative Proceeding, 1991 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - State Aid to Localities, undated (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - State School Aid Formula - JLARC Recommendations, undated (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Tidal Wetlands, undated (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Transportation, undated (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Transportation, undated (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Transportation (Finance) Chairman, 1990-1991 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Truck Routing Map, undated (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Tuition Savings Program, undated (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Underground Injection Wells, Study of Regulation, 1991 (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Unemployment Compensation Trust Fund, 1990-1991 (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Uninsured Motorists, 1983 (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - Flannery Finance Committee, undated (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Misc., undated (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Housing Study Commission, undated (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Janelle Aviation - Leesburg, undated (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Joint Legislature Audit and Review Commission, pt 1, undated (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Joint Legislature Audit and Review Commission, pt 2, undated (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Joint Legislature Audit and Review Commission, pt 3, undated (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Bangley Forks, pt 1, undated (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Bangley Forks, pt 2, undated (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Infrastructure Revenue Resources Commission on Local and State Government, pt 1, 1990 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Infrastructure Revenue Resources Commission on Local and State Government, pt 2, 1990 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Value Engineering (pt 1), undated (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Value Engineering (pt 2), undated (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Vienna, undated (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Woodrow Wilson University, undated (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Senate Steering Committee, undated (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Comparative Price Advertising, undated (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Airports Authority, undated (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - VMI Suit Re-Admission of Women, undated (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Voluntary Formulary, undated (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Water Resources Research Center Advisory Committee Part 1, undated (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Water Resources Research Center Advisory Committee Part 1, undated (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Water Resources Research Center Advisory Committee Part 2, undated (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Acupuncture, undated (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Northern Virginia Delegation Subcommittee on Transportation, undated (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Recommendations: State Boards Part 1, undated (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Recommendations: State Boards Part 2, undated (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Recommendations: State Boards Part 3, undated (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Recommendations: State Boards Part 4, undated (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Recommendations: State Boards Part 5, undated (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Redistricting Part 1, 1991 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Redistricting Part 2, 1991 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Redistricting Part 3, 1991 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Freedom of Information Act Court, undated (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Abingdon Site - National Airport, undated (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Abortion, undated (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Administrative Process Act CLD Chairman (JLARC), undated (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture, Conservation, and Natural Resources, undated (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - AIDS Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Bypass - Western and Eastern, undated (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Caller ID, undated (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Chesapeake Bay, undated (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Commerce and Labor, undated (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Center for Innovative Technology Part 1, undated (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Center for Innovative Technology Part 2, undated (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Committee Assignments - CLD, undated (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Commuter Rail, undated (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Compensation/General Government (Finances), 1990-1991 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Constitutional Offices, Funding, 1991 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Contractor Transaction Recovery Fund, 1990 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Condoms (Information), undated (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Education Disparity, undated (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Fairfax Referendum on Government (Cost) Part 1, undated (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Fairfax Referendum on Government (Cost) Part 2, undated (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - AIDS Subcommittee Study, undated (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Constitutional Officers - JLARC Studies, undated (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - JLARC "No's,", undated (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Allocation for Secondary Roads, JLARC, undated (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Arlington and Henrico - JLARC, undated (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Federal Match - Decrease of Others Allocations, JLARC, undated (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Interstate Match - JLARC, undated (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Maintenance of City Streets - JLARC, undated (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Match with Local Funds, undated (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - JLARC, 1977 (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Overall Allocation of Highway Funds - JLARC, undated (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - Primary Road Allocation - JLARC, undated (Box 138, Folder 15)
    - Unpaved Sec. Road - JLARC, undated (Box 138, Folder 16)
    - Urban System Highway Construction Funds - JLARC, undated (Box 138, Folder 17)
    - JLARC Transportation Study, 1984 (Box 138, Folder 18)
    - Housing Study Part 1, 1987-1988 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Housing Study Part 2, 1987-1988 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Legislation Part 1, 1988 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Legislation Part 2, 1988 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Legislation Part 3, 1988 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - National Technology Library Part 1, undated (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - National Technology Library Part 2, undated (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Northern Virginia Highway Construction Office Part 1, undated (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Northern Virginia Highway Construction Office Part 2, undated (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Wolf Trap Foundation Part 1, undated (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Wolf Trap Foundation Part 2, undated (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - WNVC Land Problem (Highway), undated (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Housing Study Part 1, undated (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Housing Study Part 2, undated (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Wood Burning Stoves, undated (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Wolf Trap Ramps, Dulles Toll Road, undated (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - Wolf Trap Nursery, undated (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - Silver Haired Legislature, undated (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Second Manassas Battlefield - William Shopping Mall, undated (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - United Way, 1988 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Violent Criminals and Drug Traffickers - Stiffer Action, undated (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Rules - SJRs, 1991 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Budget: Homeless, undated (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Budget: Housing Partnership Fund, undated (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Budget: Mental Health, undated (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Budget: W and OD Trail, undated (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Covered Coal Train Car Bill, undated (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Divorcement / Open Supply / Gas, undated (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Early Retirement, undated (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia State Board of Elections, undated (Box 153, Folder 19)
    - Governor and the Legislature, undated (Box 153, Folder 22)
    - Family Life Education Program, undated (Box 153, Folder 23)
    - Radon Gas, undated (Box 153, Folder 24)
    - Surveys, undated (Box 153, Folder 25)
    - C and P Rate Case Materials - Opening Statements, pt 1, undated (Box 153, Folder 26)
    - C and P Rate Case Materials - CLD Releases, pt 2, undated (Box 153, Folder 27)
    - C and P Rate Case Materials - Commission, pt 3, undated (Box 153, Folder 28)
    - C and P Rate Case Materials - Divestiture, Speculative, etc., pt 4, undated (Box 153, Folder 29)
    - C and P Rate Case Materials - Expenses of Rate Case, pt 5, undated (Box 153, Folder 30)
    - C and P Rate Case Materials - Average Rate of Various Bill Operating Subsidiaries, pt 6, undated (Box 153, Folder 31)
    - C and P Rate Case Materials - Protests and Notice of Protests, pt 7, undated (Box 153, Folder 32)
    - C and P Rate Case Materials - Rates of Return, pt 8, undated (Box 153, Folder 33)
    - C and P Rate Case Materials - Recommendations, CLD, pt 9, undated (Box 153, Folder 34)
    - C and P Rate Case Materials - Tel Operations Areas in Virginia, pt 10, undated (Box 153, Folder 35)
    - C and P Rate Case Materials - Universal Services Policy, pt 11, undated (Box 153, Folder 36)
    - Conference, pt 1, 1991 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Conference, pt 2, 1991 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Conference, pt 3, 1991 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Conference, pt 4, 1991 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Conference, pt 5, 1991 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Conference, pt 6, 1991 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Project Discovery of Virginia, Inc., 1989-1990 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Northern Virginia Planning District Commission Legislative Package, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Senate Procedures Manual, 1988 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Unclaimed Property, undated (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - News clippings, Legislation, 1975 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - News clippings, Legislation, undated (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - News clippings, Legislation, undated (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Election Law Changes, 1982 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Proposed Energy Assessment, Virginia, undated (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Wesley Housing Development Corporation, undated (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - "Today's Woman," Christian Science Monitor, undated (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Transportation, undated (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Nursing Homes, undated (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - Nursing Homes, undated (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - Nursing Homes, undated (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - Information on Richmond, undated (Box 160, Folder 15)
    - Salona, undated (Box 160, Folder 16)
    - Retiree Benefits, 1974-1975 (Box 160, Folder 17)
    - Retiree Benefits, 1974-1975 (Box 160, Folder 18)
    - Engrossed Bills, 1975 (Box 160, Folder 19)
    - Additional Information on 1975 Bills, "How They Voted,", undated (Box 160, Folder 20)
    - Elm Street Overpass, undated (Box 160, Folder 21)
    - Returnable Containers, undated (Box 160, Folder 22)
    - Etlin Case, undated (Box 160, Folder 23)
    - Welfare, undated (Box 160, Folder 24)
    - Joseph Giarratano, undated (Box 160, Folder 25)
    - Doll, Carl and Patricia/Kings Crossing Store, undated (Box 160, Folder 26)
    - Great Falls Street, undated (Box 160, Folder 27)
    - Great Falls Street, undated (Box 160, Folder 28)
    - Acupuncture, undated (Box 160, Folder 29)
    - Fairfax County, undated (Box 160, Folder 30)
    - Gift Lots, undated (Box 160, Folder 31)
    - Tree Conservation Ordinance, undated (Box 160, Folder 32)
    - Aids Study Commission, undated (Box 160, Folder 33)
    - Transportation, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 34)
    - Skippy, inc., undated (Box 160, Folder 35)
    - Retiree's State Income Tax, undated (Box 160, Folder 36)
    - Constituent Problems - Autism, undated (Box 160, Folder 37)
    - Gypsy Moth Program, undated (Box 160, Folder 38)
    - Subcommittees and Commissions, undated (Box 160, Folder 39)
    - Virginia Tuition Savings Program, undated (Box 160, Folder 40)
    - Lottery Information, undated (Box 160, Folder 41)
    - Budget Proposals and Amendments of Particular Interest to Northern Virginia, 1988 (Box 160, Folder 42)
    - DuVal Budget Amendments, 1988 (Box 160, Folder 43)
    - Budget Amendments, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 44)
    - Budget: Taxing Retirees, undated (Box 160, Folder 45)
    - Transportation - Smith Commission, undated (Box 160, Folder 46)
    - Howard Flint - Mental Health, undated (Box 160, Folder 47)
    - CLD - Bio and Statement, undated (Box 160, Folder 48)
    - Committees, Subcommittees, Commissions, Boards, etc., 1990-1991 (Box 160, Folder 49)
    - Lazarus at the Gate, undated (Box 160, Folder 50)
    - Eleanor Thompson, undated (Box 160, Folder 51)
    - Kepone, undated (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - ERA, undated (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Virginians for Dulles (Concorde), undated (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - S57 Chapter 682, undated (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - C and P Telephone, undated (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Vepco, undated (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Status of Bills, 1977 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - I66 and Metro, undated (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - Approved Bills, 1976 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Sample General Assembly Letters, undated (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - General Assembly, 1976 (Box 161, Folder 12)
    - Bills, 1977 (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - Bill Status, 1976 (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - Clive DuVal's Bills Status, 1976 (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - Legislative Districts - CLD's Complaint, undated (Box 161, Folder 16)
    - Conflict of Interest - CLD, undated (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - Ready Reference, undated (Box 161, Folder 18)
    - Ted Kennedy and Jimmy Carter, undated (Box 161, Folder 19)
    - Dorothy McDiarmid, undated (Box 161, Folder 20)
    - Gas - Virginia Fuel Distribution Plan, undated (Box 161, Folder 21)
    - Campbell, Russell Bell, undated (Box 161, Folder 22)
    - Youth Camp Safety Legislation, undated (Box 161, Folder 23)
    - Tuition Aid, undated (Box 161, Folder 24)
    - DuVal - Trees, undated (Box 161, Folder 25)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1975 (Box 161, Folder 26)
    - Status of Bills, 1975 (Box 161, Folder 27)
    - Status File, 1974 (Box 161, Folder 28)
    - Clive DuVal's Bills, 1974 (Box 161, Folder 29)
    - General Assembly, 1979 (Box 161, Folder 33)
    - Clive DuVal Biography, undated (Box 161, Folder 34)
    - Joe Gartlan, undated (Box 161, Folder 35)
    - Spina Bifida, undated (Box 161, Folder 36)
    - General Assembly, Miscellaneous Bills, 1980 (Box 161, Folder 37)
    - DuVal - Casemont Drive, undated (Box 161, Folder 38)
    - General Assembly, 1982 (Box 161, Folder 39)
    - General Assembly, 1982 (Box 161, Folder 40)
    - Chesterbrook Road, undated (Box 161, Folder 41)
    - Chesterbrook Road, undated (Box 161, Folder 42)
    - Dorothy S. McNamara, Legal Problem, undated (Box 161, Folder 43)
    - General Assembly, 1986 (Box 161, Folder 44)
    - Englat Construction Company, undated (Box 161, Folder 45)
    - Legislation, 1989 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Clive DuVal, April 1991 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Clive DuVal, March 1991 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Clive DuVal, February 1991 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Special Interests, undated (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Finances, undated (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Wilder/Chichester for Lt. Gov., undated (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Agenda Joint Meeting of Senate Finance, House Appropriations and House Finance Committees, December 18, 1987 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Learning to Retirement, undated (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Polls and Miscellaneous, undated (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - Senate Bills, 1986-1987 (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Agenda, Senate Finance Committee, June 10, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Lists House and Senate, undated (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - Budget and Miscellaneous, undated (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - Conflict of Interest Amendments and Saving and Loan Bills, 1983 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Northern Virginia Transportation Com. Rapid Transit, etc., 1966 (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Redistricting, Congressional, 1966 (Box 164, Folder 10)
    - Opening Statements, Past Vepco Cases, Cross-x of W's, 1966 (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Wesley Housing Development Corporation, undated (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - Vepco, undated (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - Value Engineering, undated (Box 165, Folder 11)
    - Transportation Funds - Fair Share for Northern Virginia, undated (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - Redskin Stadium - Alexandria, undated (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - Recommendations: Schools, undated (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Recommendations: Schools, undated (Box 165, Folder 15)
    - Disney Project, 1994 (Box 165, Folder 16)
    - C and P Telephone - SCC Review of Current Rates, undated (Box 165, Folder 17)
    - Caller ID, undated (Box 165, Folder 18)
    - Clean Air Act, undated (Box 165, Folder 19)
    - Survey of Political Attitudes, May 1965 (Box 165, Folder 20)
    - Dulles High Occupancy Vehicle (HOV) Lanes, undated (Box 165, Folder 22)
    - Acupuncture, undated (Box 165, Folder 23)
    - Arlington County, undated (Box 165, Folder 24)
    - Study of Political Opinions in Virginia, June 1970 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Recommendations: Schools, undated (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Natural Resources Bond Com., 1992 (Box 166, Folder 12)
    - General Assembly Session, 1988 (Box 166, Folder 13)
    - Briefing of Declaration of Trans., etc., undated (Box 166, Folder 14)
    - Fairfax Journal Article (Starns), undated (Box 166, Folder 15)
    - Equal Rights Amendment Information, undated (Box 166, Folder 16)
    - Study of Virginia's 10th Congressional District, April 1962 (Box 166, Folder 17)
    - Legislation, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - BLDG 193 Fort Belvoir Clippings, 1987 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - New Dominion, undated (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Record, January-February 1985 (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Record, January-February 1986 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Record, January-February 1987 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Picture Yourself, undated (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Clive DuVal - Virginia Hospital Association, January 1984 (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Washington Airports Task Force directory, 1990-1991 (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Northern Virginia Delegation, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Senate Finance Committee, 1991 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - CD Legislative Records, undated (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Typical Electric Bills, undated (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Salona, September 26, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Human Resources Agency Fact Sheets, undated (Box 171, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Record, 1989 (Box 171, Folder 11)
    - Virginia State Publications, July 1, 1988 (Box 171, Folder 12)
    - Virginia, 1990 (Box 171, Folder 13)
    - Senate and House of Delegates, 1991 (Box 171, Folder 14)
    - Civic Association Information, undated (Box 171, Folder 15)
    - Wildlife Abundance Through Forestry, undated (Box 171, Folder 16)
    - Session of the Virginia General Assembly, 1991 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Fairfax Committee of 100, undated (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Summary Fair Elections Practices Act, July 1, 1991 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Election Laws, 1991 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Standing Rules of the Senate, undated (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Handbook for Public Officers and Employees on the Comprehensive Conflict of Interests Act, July 1, 1983 (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Finance Committee, 1987 (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Address and Other Senate Information, undated (Box 172, Folder 10)
- Series 3: Campaign Materials, 1960-1994
  This series contains notes for speeches, legislator survey responses, fund-raising files, reports of campaign contributions and expenditures, declaration of candidacy certificates, election tallies, brochures, position papers, and press releases and clipping files.
  - Virginia Political Campaign [scrapbook A], 1965-1966 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Political Campaign [scrapbook B], 1965-1966 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Political Campaign [scrapbook C], 1965-1966 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Materials, 1960 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Questionnaires, 1966-1969 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Materials, 1970s (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - US Senate Campaign, Press Releases, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - CLD Legislative Record in Senate, 1972-1983 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - US Senate Campaign, Senator Clive DuVal, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - US Senate Campaign, DuVal Introduction, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - US Senate Campaign, Invitation and Letters, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - US Senate Campaign, Speeches, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - US Senate Campaign, Press Releases, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - US Senate Campaign, "Better Health,", 1978 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - US Senate Campaign, "Consumer,", 1978 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - US Senate Campaign, "Education,", 1978 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - US Senate Campaign, "Environment,", 1978 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - US Senate Campaign, "Human Rights,", 1978 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - US Senate Campaign, "Open Government,", 1978 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - US Senate Campaign, "Progress,", 1978 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - US Senate Campaign, "Unemployment,", 1978 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - US Senate Campaign, "Women,", 1978 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - US Senate Campaign, "Working Virginians,", 1978 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - US Senate Campaign, "Issues,", 1978 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - US Senate Campaign, Clippings File, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - US Senate Campaign, Newspaper List for NOVA, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - US Senate Campaign, Reception Sign-in Form, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - US Senate Campaign, Ira Lechner Letterhead, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - US Senate Campaign, Bumper Stickers, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - State Senate Election, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising for 1977 and 1981 Campaigns, 1977-1981 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - 1983 Campaign (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Announcement Statements, undated (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Master Copies - Position Papers, undated (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Nuclear Power Plants/Nuclear Freeze, also Church Valley, undated (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Campaign Issues and "Secret 5,", 1983 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Campaign Materials, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    1987
  - Northern Virginia Delegation (pt 1), 1983-1984 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Northern Virginia Delegation (pt 2), 1983-1984 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Northern Virginia Delegation (pt 3), 1988 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Northern Virginia Delegation (pt 4), 1988 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Gramm Rudman Fund-Raising Letters, undated (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Northern Virginia Delegation, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Questionnaires, undated (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Scheduled Speeches, 1987 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous - Kilmer's Letter to DuVal, undated (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Voting Results, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Literature Kilberg, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Information (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Thank You Letters, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Boucher Fundraiser, Salona, June 20, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 3)